Daniel J. Lee

3004 Suncrest Drive, San Diego, CA 92116

Dan.lee619@gmail.com

http://DanLee619.github.io

https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniellee619

(619) 415-6367

Summary

Cisco Networking Academy graduate with outstanding written and verbal communication skills. A quick learner with experience working in high-pressure environments demanding inter-personal collaboration. Competent in a wide variety of programming languages. Experienced in cabling, troubleshooting, and setting up networks.

Technical Skills

Routing & Switching: OSPF, EIGRP, RIP, BGP, RSTP, PVST+, ACLs, PAGP/LACP, PPPoE, GRE, IPsec, HSRP, Port-security Configurations, Spanning tree, VPNs, DHCP, DNS

Programming: Java, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, html5, CSS3

Education

Cisco Networking Academy

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)

San Diego Community Colleges (Mesa and Southwestern)

Completed 49 Units in Computer Science and IT

·

University of California Santa Barbara *BA in Film and Media Studies; 3.7 GPA*

Work Experience

Team Lead 2014 - Present

The Party Staff Inc.

- Act as liaison between clients and home office.
- Manage Party Staff employees to ensure that all work is done to client's satisfaction.
- Create event reports and perform other event related data-entry functions.

Marketing and Promotions Assistant

2014 - 2016

2016

2011

2013-2015

Comedy Juice

- Manage online marketing and promote upcoming shows via social media.
- Coordinate promotions and partnerships with local businesses.
- Operate the lights and soundboard for shows.